Enthusiastic full-stack developer with 3+ years professional web & software development experience in fast-paced, multi-cultural work environment both locally and overseas. Have proven outstanding problem-solving skills and diverse skill sets.

Passionate about learning and adapting new technologies and enjoy understanding how things can be used in different approaches to achieve desired goals. Love to collaborate with team and self-driven when assigned to work on independent tasks.

# **Work History**

# 2021-05 -Current

# **Digital Developer**

Lime Digital, Auckland

- Created custom template websites in various CMS:
   Wordpress/WooCommerce, Shopify, Drupal etc.
- Implemented digital strategies to increase website traffic, security and performance.
- Liaised between marketing and IT on web development projects integrating front-end assets to back-end systems.
- Researched emerging web technologies and trends for possible incorporation into sites.

2019-03 -2021-03

# Web & Software Engineer

Timerec Ltd, Shanghai, Auckland

- Participated in cross-platform application architecture, design and implementation of front-end UI components using HTML5, SCSS,
   Vue.js and back-end features using Java, Python and SQL.
- Developed backstage management system to manage API-centric infrastructures, Data Analytics and Visualization from relational database.
- Designed enhancements and updates for subsystems of end-user applications running on local and cloud platforms.

# Education

2018-07 -2020-01

# Bachelor of Information Sciences: Information Technology

Massey University - Auckland

- Completed web development course with A- grade.
- Managed to finish study in distance learning during internship to full-time work in China.

2016-07 -2018-01

# **Statistics And Computer Science**

The University of Auckland

- Completed Statistics and Data Modeling course with A grade.
- Student tutor for University courses

### **Portfolio**



# Jonny Cui

Full-stack Web Developer

### Contact

Address

North Shore, Auckland, 0630

Phone

021-027-01324

E-mail

jyc1129@live.com

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/jonny-cui/

## **Skills**

# HTML & CSS Excellent JavaScript Very Good Wordpress Excellent PHP Good Java Good Python Good SQL Good UI/UX Design

Digital Marketing

Good

Good

**Project Management** 

Good

Cloud Infrastructure

Good

Data Analysis and Visulisation

Good

View my portfolio at JonnyCui.github.io